<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Project_Onyx</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">DetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="transname">Hiiiiiii!</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="mindspark_content"><i>"It is marvelling how eloquent a discussion can get. Steadily climbing the intricate scaffolds of logic, beliefs, ideas and whatnot. One encounters different perspectives and ideologies which is impossible to achieve on our own. It is an exchange of knowledge and rationality which aims not for victory but for progress and helps us descend to a sense of agreement.

        "Freedom is hammered on the anvil of discussion, a spirit of collaboration and progress".</i>

Come and bang down the latched doors of ignorance at <b>Mindspark</b>!

Let’s create a better society.

MindSpark is an open platform for speaking up your views and opinions on the burning issues of the day. MindSpark has been an effective medium at bringing up solutions to social problems as it involves open ended viewpoints which run far beyond ordinary vision. Be at MindSpark and shake the ignorance and narrow mindedness of the spectators by digging facts and figures. (which will be monitored by our esteemed panellists)

Rules-
Standard conduct of Group Discussion applies to MindSpark.

Round 1
UNMODERATED CAUCUSS
1- Each individual will be given 2 min for constructive speech followed by interjection.
2- 3mins from other participants
3- One formal question from judges.
4-  each required to give at least one solution for agenda of the house.

Round 2
PERSUASION ROUND
In this round each individual will make an appeal to the masses on "why their solution is most appropriate."
On the basis of voting we will decide the best solution.
1min will be to each speaker to make their appeal.

Both English and Hindi are allowed as language of discussion.

Registration Fee- Rs 50"</string>

    <string name="how_it_content">What would it be if your favourite movies had ended differently? How about if your favourite character had turned evil at the last minute or the villain grew a heart suddenly. Give the stories a taste of your own style and version. Make and create an alternate life for your favourite characters or give them an ending which satisfies you and only you. Will your story ending be happy, sad or somewhere between the two? Will you tie everything up, or do you plan to leave loose ends?
        So come one and come all to "How it should have ended" and make your imaginations soar high in skies.

\n\nTime: 45 min

\nSetting: The participants will already be informed of the movies they can write about. They can think and prepare beforehand.

\n\nRules: The participants will be given a random chit with some particular scene / prop. The participants will have to write the story of the movie while incorporating the said task.

<b>Registration fees</b>: ₹50</string>

    <string name="ship_content">You are given the role of Superman/ Justin Bieber/ Narendra Modi etc. The ship is sinking, and the Captain has only one Life-Jacket left. You are on the ship with other famous celebrities/ fictional characters/ hypothetical characters. So step into the shoes of the given character and try to escape from the sinking ship by using your impressive , convincing skills and prove that you deserve the only Life-Jacket. Make yourself appear prominent and better than any other person/ thing on board to win the Life-Jacket and eventually win the event.

\n\nRules : \n1). Use yours words to win and no special powers.
\n2). Impress the judges within the time limit of 15-20 minutes ( duration can vary and be changed at the start of the event ).
\n\nRegistration fee - Rs 50</string>

    <string name="got_content"> Misplaced Royalties and Misjudged Loyalties ,
\nThe dead Kings, and the Unruly Queens,
\nThe Empathic mercenary, and the Unthinking Dead,
\nComes A Song of Fire and Ice with Six Houses and Seven Kingdoms.
\n\nWe know the Faith of the North, the story of Westeros, the Beliefs of the South and the prophecy of the Undead. But Good ol’ George knows how to keep the audience glued to their chairs. And so do we.
        \nThis Onyx, we bring you something that calls for Bran’s knowledge, Cersie’s commitment and Baelish-ish trickery.  Organizing this event might be like selling poison to the unsuspecting, but there is nobody making us atone for our sins…anymore.

\n\n• The first Round will consist of a Quiz where you have to answer the questions put up by the quiz master. Make sure you collect points to survive our treachery.

\n• ‎The second round will comprise of enactment of a character from Game of Thrones wherein one among a team has to enact. The other team members will have to guess the character.The actor will get 30 seconds to plan, and next 30 seconds to enact. If you don’t get it right, just hope the other teams don’t too.

\n• ‎The most requiring round will be the “Hunt For Dragonglass”, the Treasure Hunt. The teams will be provided with clues and will have to search for props. The more Dragonglass you have, the better equipped you are for the Battle against the Walkers.

\n• ‎The team with the maximum number of dragonglass wins, but remember, there’s only place for one person on the Iron Throne.

\n\nRegistration Fee- Rs 50</string>

    <string name="gangs_content"><i>“Ye wasseypur hai. Yahaan kabootar bhi ek pankh se udhta hai…aur doosre se apni izzat bachata hai!”</i>


\n\nWe all remember this famous dialogue from the movie, Gangs of Wasseypur. It’s avant-garde, raw and off the beat which makes it an absolutely riveting experience. So, we are bringing together a number of movies of the same genre to create an event "gangs of wasseypur".
\nThis February ,for the first time in the history of ONYX , the audience will witness  a kick-ass event based on Gangs of Wasseypur ,one of the most iconic movie franchises of Bollywood. An event, created  for all the people who would love to step out of their homes to enjoy their favourite film. But, this event isn\'t confined within the walls of multiplexes and will instead be held in open air! The event has a fantastic line up of exciting and entertaining activities alongwith clan wars and treasure hunt because screening a movie to relive it is just too mainstream.
\n\nWAIT…  there will be loads of prizes to be won too. So get ready for experiencing something really exciting ,raw , funny ,EXPLICIT ;-)  and full of entertainment.


\nTotal of 4 teams will be shortlisted for the Main round
\nRound 3 :
MURDER MYSTERY

\n<i>"Never theorise before you have data.
Invariably, you end up twisting facts to suit theories, instead of theories to suit facts."</i>
\n\nThe night is dark and full of terrors, so is the case. Solve the case, perform the
tasks and find the Murderer.
\n\nRULES
\n1. Each team shall comprise of 4 Participants only.
\n2. Participants will have to solve cases with the help of clues and tasks.
(similar to Treasure Hunt)
\n3. Use of cell phones or any other device for communication is strictly
prohibited.
\n4. No team shall try to communicate with any other team or take any help
from the volunteers.
\n5. The event will be held within the college premises only.
\n6. The decisions of the coordinators will be final and binding.
\n7. The Management shall not be held responsible for any kind of injury
caused in the course of this event.
\n8. Use of expletives or aggressive behaviour will result in immediate
disqualification.
\n\nReg. Fee : 50
       \n <b>#YO_Onyx</b></string>

    <string name="poetry_content">"Poetry is just the evidence of life. If your life is burning well, poetry is just the ash."-Leonard Cohen

You all must have tapped  feet to the beats of:
"Let her go" and "I hate" - Passenger
"Love yourself"- Justin Beiber
Have you ever wondered about the poems which touched your soul?
"Afreen afreen" written by Mr. Javed Akhtar and "Ek pyaar ka nagma hai" by Santosh Anand are some of the poems that came out as few of the most popular songs.

      \n \n <i>"If there’s a poem inside of you, it needs to come out. I want people to think of poetry as more human, less sacred"</i>
- Sarah Kay
\n\nIt is not necessary to be born with poetic skills but to have a passion for writing is a choice one makes.
Poetry is the expression of the deepest feeling that one has.
Those who scribble on train walls, the tumblr poets, the facebook poets and the not-so-romantic poets ,YOU ARE ALL INVITED TO  the  poetry event - "Kavi Sammelan" at our Literary Fest.
Write and recite your deepest feelings and rebuild your fractured confidence.
\n\nRULES:

\n1) We will have 3 rounds.

\n2) First round is open to all.

\n3) The first round would require the participants to write a poem based on a collage shown to them.

\n4) The  second round would require the participants to write a poem expanding the given 4 lines.

\nThe poems can either be in Hindi or English.
Hinglish is NOT allowed.

The participants will be judged on:
Use of language (Hinglish is NOT allowed)
Use of poetic devices like assonance, alliteration etc.
Use of rhyming scheme.

\n5) The final round will consist of an open mic.
The participants who will qualify in the second round will recite their respective poems in the open mic.

\nIn addition to this, we will have a fun round in between so that the participants do not get bored while waiting for the results. For this, a line from a poem or song will be given to the participants and they will have to complete it using their own words. People with the fastest and most interesting answers will get rewards.

       \n\n Registration Fee: Rs. 50
</string>
    <string name="content_1"></string>
    <string name="content_2"></string>
</resources>
